<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction on Quartermaster - Documentation</title>
    <link>https://qmstr.org/documentation/introduction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Introduction on Quartermaster - Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 15:26:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://qmstr.org/documentation/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What is QMSTR?</title>
      <link>https://qmstr.org/documentation/introduction/what-is-qmstr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qmstr.org/documentation/introduction/what-is-qmstr/</guid>
      <description>Quartermaster is an integrated free and open source software (FOSS) toolchain that implements industry best practises of license compliance management. It is FOSS because the QMSTR community believes that software that manages FOSS compliance becomes critical infrastructure to the wider open source community and should itself be FOSS. QMSTR is developed in collaboration with users, legal experts and other interested stakeholders.
QMSTR: A command-line workflow toolchain for FOSS compliance QMSTR is implemented as a command line toolchain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why QMSTR?</title>
      <link>https://qmstr.org/documentation/introduction/why-qmstr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qmstr.org/documentation/introduction/why-qmstr/</guid>
      <description>A key impulse for the development of QMSTR was the realization that there is still no industry standard for FOSS compliance tooling, and the understanding that the management of software copyright and license compliance in FOSS needs to improve. While from a legal perspective, every obligation and liability technically boils down to managing the risk of running into trouble and the mitigation of possible damage, we believe that this is not the right mindset to approach FOSS license compliance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>