<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sprint on The Quartermaster project.</title>
    <link>https://qmstr.org/tags/sprint/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sprint on The Quartermaster project.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 08:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://qmstr.org/tags/sprint/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quartermaster Sprint 4.3 Development Report: Documentation, documentation, documentation</title>
      <link>https://qmstr.org/blog/2019/04/03/qmstr-sprint-4.3-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qmstr.org/blog/2019/04/03/qmstr-sprint-4.3-report/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The QMSTR sprints 4.2 and 4.3 (this report covers both) are part of
our current efforts to merge the ongoing QMSTR development and the
FASTEN project. A key necessity for this was documentation. Everybody
loves to write documentation, especially developers. Right? :-) To
make it even more fun, we work on integrating end user and
administrator documentation with the project source code and perform
automated integration test automatically. We hope that this approach
leads to documentation that works and is reliable. Even though this
effort is still ongoing, some results are already visible. One of them
is the project documentation on the main web site. Some feature
development primarily on the node management command line interface is
also in progress. It should be finished in time for the QMSTR 0.4
release, planned for April 17.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quartermaster Sprint 4.1 Development Report: Go, Java and Python integration libraries</title>
      <link>https://qmstr.org/blog/2019/02/20/qmstr-sprint-4.1-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qmstr.org/blog/2019/02/20/qmstr-sprint-4.1-report/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The key goal of QMSTR milestone 4 is to stabilize the APIs and
streamline the documentation and tutorials to prepare the integration
with the development work that takes part in
the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.fasten-project.eu/&#34;&gt;FASTEN project&lt;/a&gt; and
in
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linuxfoundation.org/press-release/2018/12/the-linux-foundation-to-launch-new-tooling-project-to-improve-open-source-compliance/&#34;&gt;ACT&lt;/a&gt;. To
prepare for that, sprint 4.1 focused on refactoring the integration
libraries for Go, Java and Python that developers use to
create &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/QMSTR&#34;&gt;QMSTR&lt;/a&gt; modules and client side
tools. These libraries help users to create diverse sets of modules
and client side code to fit their needs, and facilitate the
integration with various services like CI/CD environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>